History has a violent way of repeating itself.
Exit Humanity is a drama, horror film directed by John Geddes.
A decade after the American Civil War, Edward Young returns home from a hunting trip to find
a horrific reanimation of his wife and that their son Adam has disappeared.
He must battle his way through an unexplainable outbreak of the walking dead.
Medic Johnson, played by Stephen McHattie.
Malcolm Young (voice), played by Brian Cox.
Edward Young, played by Mark Gibson.
Wayne, played by Ari Millen.
Emma, played by Jordan Hayes.
Eve, played by Dee Wallace.
Exit Humanity is a 2011 Canadian period zombie horror film directed by John Geddes, starring Mark Gibson, Adam
Seybold, Jordan Hayes, Dee Wallace, Bill Moseley, Stephen McHattie, Ari Millen and Jason David Brown.
The tone is dark and emotional.